-Phoebe, could you get that, please?
-Why?
전화 좀 받아줄래?
왜? 네 엉덩이는 너무
무거워서 안 떨어지니?
Just because you're too lazy
to get up off your tushy?
No, it's just that all the people in the world
I would want to talk to are right here.
아니, 내가 대화하고 싶은
유일한 사람은 여기 있거든
그렇담 뭐
Sucker.
바보...
Hello?
여보세요?
-Hey, Joey!
-Hey, Phoebe.
- 조이구나
- 안녕, 피비
저기, 부탁이 있어서
I need a favor.
I forgot the PlN to my ATM card.
Can you get it for me?
현금카드 비밀번호를
잊어버렸는데 찾아봐줄래?
Sure. Where is it?
그래, 어디 있는데?
길모퉁이에 있는
현금인출기에 새겨놨어
I scratched it on the ATM machine
on the corner.
그럼 5639가 네 번호야?
So you're 5-6-3-9?
That's it! Thanks.
바로 그거야
고맙다, 피비
챈들러랑 통화할래?
-Wanna talk to Chandler?
-Let me talk to him.
조이면 나 좀 바꿔줘
He didn't believe in my movie...
싫어, 내 영화를 우습게 본 놈
까불지 말라고 해
이건 진짜야, 진짜라고
...which is a big mistake,
because it is real. Real.
이봐, 트리비아니
Tribbiani, get back to work.
Break time's over.
자기 위치로 가
휴식시간 끝났어
-Who was that?
-My stunt double. Yeah.
- 그 사람 누구야?
- 내 스턴트 대역
이젠 아예 기어오른다
He's getting a little too familiar
for my tastes.
일주일 내내 사과하려고 했어
그렇게 통화하기 싫으면
I've tried to apologize.
If I can't do it on the phone,
I'll go and do it in person.
내가 직접 가서 대면하겠어
I heard that. Can you put him on?
피비, 나도 들었어
바꿔줄래?
- 나다
- 오긴 어딜 와
Don't come out here.
난 전적으로 네 편이야
가서 직접 증명하겠어
I support you 100% and I wanna prove
that to you in person.
알았어, 용서할게
오지 말라니깐
I got that. I forgive you.
Don't come out here.
용서? 일주일 동안
상대도 안 해주더니
You haven't taken
my calls for a week.
다 풀렸어, 친구는 영원해
절대 오지 마
I'm totally over it. Friends forever.
Don't come out here.
Would you mind doing
a picture with us?
사진 좀 같이 찍을까요?
-What was that?
-Entertainment Tonight.
- 그건 뭐지?
- 연예가 중계
어쨌든 알아들었으니까
오지 마, 됐지?
Good talking to you
and don't come out here.
그러시죠
The One in Vegas
Monica? I'm sorry I'm late.
모니카? 늦어서 미안해
모니카?
피비?
I'm so sorry.
Have you been here long?
정말 미안하다
- 오래 기다렸어?
- 됐어
That's okay.
What the hell took you so long?
뭐하다 이제 온 거야?
좋아, 챈들러한텐 비밀이야
우연히 리처드를 만났어
You can't tell Chandler.
I ran into Richard.
-Which Richard?
-The Richard.
어떤 리처드?
- 그 리처드
- 리처드 시몬스? 어머!
Richard Simmons? Oh, my God!
아니, 나랑 사귀던 리처드
알잖아, 훤칠하고 콧수염에...
No, my ex-boyfriend Richard.
You know, the tall guy, mustache.
하긴 그래야 말이 되지
Okay, that actually
makes more sense. How was it?
어땠어?
아주 좋았어, 얘기하다
점심까지 같이 먹었어
It was really nice. We talked
and I had lunch with him.
신기해라, 네가 리처드랑
점심 먹는 꿈을 꿨는데
That's weird. I dreamed
you had lunch with Richard.
-Really?
-Again, Richard Simmons.
- 정말?
- 그것도 리처드 시몬스야
Go on.
그래서?
The strange part was
he was really nice...
참 이상하지? 그 사람
무지 친절하고 근사했는데
...and he looks great,
but I didn't feel anything.
아무 느낌도 없는 거야
근데 왜 챈들러한텐 비밀로 해?
So why can't we tell Chandler?
분명 난리칠 거야
It'll freak him out and tomorrow's our
anniversary. I don't wanna spoil it.
내일 우리 1주년인데
분위기 망치기 싫어
벌써 1년이나 됐다니
믿어지지가 않는다
I can't believe you guys
have lasted a whole year!
레이첼한테 20달러 빚졌네
Wow, I owe Rachel 20 bucks.
- 뭐?
- 전혀 다른 내기였어
On a totally different bet.
나야
-It's almost our anniversary!
-I know.
- 내일이 1주년이야
- 알아
One year ago today, I was just
your annoying friend Chandler.
믿어져? 1년 전 오늘 난 단지
너의 귀찮은 친구였을 뿐인데
Now you're just
my annoying friend Chandler.
지금은 내 귀찮은 친구지
I got you a gift.
- 선물 준비했어
- 기념일은 내일이잖아
-It's not till tomorrow.
-I know, but you have to open it today.
- 그래도 오늘 열어봐
- 좋아
알았어, 이리 내
Okay! There you go!
It's two tickets to Vegas!
라스베이거스행 티켓 두 장
그래! 이번 주말이야
Yeah! For this weekend!
It'll be perfect.
완벽하잖아
You'll see Joey, plus, we'll start
our celebration on the plane.
조이도 볼 수 있고 비행기에서
1주년 기념식을 거행하는 거야
이렇게 부르자
'비행기념일'
We can call it our "Plane-aversary."
Do we have to?
꼭 그래야 돼?
아니
This is great, but Joey didn't want
any of us there.
멋진 계획이지만
조이가 오지 말라던데
우리 고생할까봐 그런 거지
He doesn't want us to go to any trouble.
He'll be excited when we surprise him.
갑자기 나타나면
얼마나 좋아하겠어
게다가 우리만의
'기념베가스일'도 있잖아
Plus, we get to have
our own "Anna-Vegas-ry"!
'기념네바다일'
"Anna-vada-versary!"
I think we should see other people.
우리 다른 사람도 좀 만나보자
We can go, right?
- 가는 거지, 응?
- 그래
멋진 생각이야
Great idea.
좋아, 나도 갈래!
I'm gonna go too!
Phoebe, it's kind of
our anniversary.
이건 우리 기념일이야
You won't ditch me
like you did with London.
런던 갈 때처럼
또 따돌릴 생각 마
Ditch you?
You were pregnant
따돌리다니
넌 그때 임신 중이라...
알았으니까 나도 가
Great story. I'm going.
- 나 왔다
- 왔구나
얘들아, 들어봐
Listen, this weekend we're all gonna go
to Las Vegas to surprise Joey!
이번 주말에 우리 모두 조이
놀래주러 라스베이거스에 간다
나도 같이!
Including me!
Do you wanna go?
너희도 갈래?
I can take a couple days off work.
이틀 정도는 휴가 낼 수 있어
당연히 휴가를 내야지
이번 여행엔 나도 끼니까!
Of course you can take a couple days
off, because this trip includes me!
잠깐, 내일 프레젠테이션이
있는데 거긴 못 빠져
I've got a presentation tomorrow.
I can't miss that.
I've got tickets to the Van Gogh
exhibit. I waited a year for this.
반 고흐 전시회 입장권을 어쩐다
1년 동안이나 기다려왔는데
Art lover.
예술애호가
What'd you say?
뭐라고?
I said, art lover.
예술애호가라고 했어
-Was that supposed to be an insult?
-I don't know, I'm very tired.
- 그건 조롱이냐?
- 몰라, 무지 피곤하다
레이첼, 그럼 우린
토요일에 출발할까?
-Rach, maybe we can fly out Saturday?
-Sounds great.
- 그게 좋겠다
- 그럼 표 예약할게
I'll call the airlines.
하룻밤 이 집을 나 혼자
독차지하는 것도 좋지
That'll be nice to have
the apartment to myself.
맞아, 발가벗고
돌아다닐 수도 있고
To walk around naked.
No, so I can be by myself.
Have a little alone time.
아니, 혼자만의 오붓한
시간을 가질 수 있잖아
그래, 혼자만의 발가벗은 시간
Naked alone time.
Just because I'm alone doesn't mean
I wanna walk around naked.
혼자 있다고 꼭 알몸으로
돌아다닐 이유가 있니?
You live alone,
you don't walk around naked.
넌 혼자 살아도 안 그러잖아
내가 문 열어주는 데 시간이
오래 걸리는 이유가 뭐겠니?
Why does it takes me so long
to answer the door?
So far, is this trip to Las Vegas
better or worse than the trip to London?
지금까지 보면 이번 여행이
런던 여행보다 좋아, 나빠?
지금까지는 거의 똑같네
So far, it's pretty much
the same, Phoebe.
좋아, 내가 이 사탕을
준 뒤에는 어떨까?
What about after I give you
these candies?
I guess it's a little better now.
그럼 이번이 좀 낫다
좋아, 라스베이거스 1점
런던 0점
Las Vegas, 1.
London, 0.
I'll be back.
금방 올게
행복한 비행기념일 맞아
Happy Plane-aversary.
사랑해
I love you.
-Can I give you your present now?
-Okay!
- 지금 선물 줄까?
- 좋아!
Oh, don't tell me I did this.
내가 정신을 어따 빼놓고 다니나
선물 갖고 장난하는 거 너무 좋아!
I love "l forgot the present" fake-out!
진짜로 놓고 와서 장난치는 게
아니라 미안하다면?
How about "I did forget the present,
forgive me" not fake-out?
You can give it to me
when we get back.
괜찮아, 돌아가서 주면 되지
기념일에 일어날 수 있는
최악의 사건이다
This is the worst thing
that could happen.
You decided to tell him
about the Richard thing.
결국 리처드 사건 얘기했구나
What "Richard thing"?
- 리처드 사건이라니?
- 내가 못살아
Oh, no.
What "Richard thing"?
- 리처드 사건이 뭔데?
- 시몬스로 밀어붙여
Simmons. Go with Simmons.
좋아, 있잖아...
I ran into Richard yesterday.
어제 우연히 리처드를 만났는데
식사나 하자고 해서 같이 먹었어
He asked me if I wanted to go
for a bite and I did.
굳이 말하지 않은 건
I didn't tell you
because you'd get mad...
너 화내면 우리 기념일
망칠까봐 걱정돼서야
...and I didn't wanna spoil
our anniversary.
화 안 났어
I'm not mad.
Really?
- 정말?
- 그럼
우연히 리처드를 만나
한 끼 때운 거잖아
So you bumped into Richard.
You grabbed a "bite."
No big deal.
별거 아니구만
Great.
다행이네
좋아, 런던 1점...
Okay, London, 1.
경마가 따로 없네
This is gonna be a real horserace.
Oh, look what happened.
이를 어째
Check me out.
나 좀 봐라
주방에 서있다
I'm in my kitchen...
...naked.
홀랑 벗고
I'm picking up an orange.
오렌지 하나 들어봐?
I'm naked.
홀랑 벗고
I'm lighting the candles.
촛불을 켠다
홀랑 벗고
Naked. And carefully.
그니까 조심해서
Oh, my God! That's Rachel, naked!
맙소사, 레이첼이 벗었다
I can't look at that.
I am looking at this.
보면 안 돼
난 이걸 볼 거야
Okay, vivid colors,
expressive brush strokes.
좋아, 강렬한 색채
꿈틀거리는 붓놀림
Unless she wants me
to be looking at that.
내가 봐주길 바라는 건 아닐까?
She knows I'm home.
내가 집에 있다는 것도 알고
여기서 보인다는 것도 알아
She knows I can see her.
What kind of game is she playing?
이게 무슨 꿍꿍이 플레이지?
I think maybe someone's lonely tonight.
누군가 오늘밤 외로운갑다
Dr. Geller.
닥터 겔러, 그만둬
바보짓하지 말고
Stop it. You're being silly.
Or am I?
정말 그럴까?
Love to love you baby
그대를 향한 사랑, 아우!
Darn it!
젠장!
안녕?
May I come in?
들어가도 돼?
Yeah, if you want to.
들어오고 싶으면
내가 들어갔으면 좋겠어?
Do you want me to?
Yeah, sure?
그래, 물론
동감이야
So do l.
Okay, Rach, before anything happens...
좋아, 레이첼
뭔 일 벌이지기 전에
...I wanna lay down a couple
of ground rules.
몇 가지 기본원칙을
확실히 해두자고
This is just about tonight.
딱 오늘밤만이야
I won't go through with this
if it'll raise the question of "us."
추후 '우리 ' 문제가 다시
거론되지 않았으면 좋겠어
알았어?
난 이번 일이 그저...
I just want this to be...
...about what it is.
이 자체로 끝났으면 해
그런데 이번 일이란 게 뭐지?
And...
...what is that, Ross?
The physical act of love.
사랑의 육체적 행위
What, are you crazy?
뭐? 너 미쳤니?
방금 날 유혹한 게 아닌가?
홀랑 벗은 걸 내가 봤는데?
So you weren't trying to entice me
just now with your nakedness?
세상에, 날 봤니?
Oh, God. You saw me?
You weren't trying to entice me
with your nakedness?
날 유혹하려고
벗은 게 아니었다고?
말도 안 돼
진짜 내가 너랑
잘 거라고 생각했어?
You actually thought
I wanted to have sex with you?
맙소사
아니
아니지
아냐
아니거들랑
Oh, wow. I'm sorry. But, Ross,
you kicked off your shoes.
세상에, 어떻게
신발까지 벗어 던져?
오늘 일 그냥 잊어줄래?
-Can we just forget this ever happened?
-Of course. You're right. I'm sorry.
그럼, 알았어
괜찮아, 미안해
-Thank you.
-Yes.
- 고맙다
- 그래
난 짐이나 싸야겠다
-I guess I'm gonna go pack.
-Okay. Wait, one more thing.
참! 하나 더
Do we still need to settle
the question of "us"?
근데 아직도 해결할
'우리' 문제가 남았던가?
얘들아, 기다려
Hey, you guys, wait!
You guys.
같이 가
This place is much better than London.
런던이랑 비교가 안 된다, 그치?
A lady dressed like Cleopatra
gave me this.
클레오파트라로 분장한
여자가 이 쿠폰을 줬어
스테이크랑 바다가재가
99센트라니
Ninety-nine cent
steak and lobster dinner.
You don't eat animals.
넌 고기 안 먹잖아
For ninety-nine cents I'd eat you.
99센트면 너도 먹겠다
봐, 여기서 아예
살 수도 있겠다
I can totally settle down here.
내가 원하는 건 다 있어
It's got everything I could ever want.
Including Joey! Look!
조이까지, 저길 봐
Look! Hey!
Oh, my God.
하느님 맙소사
우리 왔어, 조이
콘돔 멋지다, 임마
Love your condoms, my man.
Why are you here?
I told you not to come.
너희들 여긴 웬일이야?
오지 말라고 했잖아
Why are you dressed as a gladiator?
왜 검투사 옷을 입었어?
그게... 지금 촬영 중이거든
Because I'm shooting a scene right now.
I play a gladiator.
검투사 역이야
잠깐만 있어봐
Hold on a second. Can we cut?
여기서 자르죠
My friends are here.
I'm gonna take a break.
친구들이 와서
잠깐 쉬어야겠는데
Who are you talking to?
누구한테 그러는 거야?
저기...
감독님한테...
The director.
Her.
이 분
All right, it's not a gladiator movie.
I work here.
그래, 검투사 영화 아냐
나 여기서 일해
Why? What happened?
왜, 어쩌다가?
제작비가 떨어져서
촬영이 중단됐어
The movie shut down.
Ran out of money.
I'm working here till it starts up,
if it ever does.
일하면서 기다리는 거야
시작될지는 모르지만
-I'm so sorry.
-Such a drag.
- 어떡하니
- 이 일을 어째
Sorry I didn't tell you.
I'm sorry.
속여서 미안해
너한테도 미안하고
뭐 괜찮아, 요즘은 서로
숨기는 게 유행인가 봐
Apparently there's
a new policy of not sharing.
- 꽁하고 있을 줄 알았어
- 너 검투사란 말이지?
-I knew you weren't okay with that.
-So you're a gladiator!
What's going on?
뭔데 그래?
-Monica had lunch with Richard.
-Dawson?
모니카가 리처드랑 점심 먹었대
도슨?
아니, 하지만 그것도 멋지다 얘
But that would've been so cool!
Her boyfriend Richard.
- 아니, 남자친구 리처드
- 아무 의미도 없어, 됐니?
It meant nothing. After all this time,
how can you not trust me?
이제 와서 날 못 믿겠어?
When you go lunching with hunky men
and don't tell me!
콧수염 허우대랑 점심 먹고
아무 말도 안 했을 땐
You're right. I'm sorry.
I should've told you.
맞아
미안해, 말했어야 하는데
Thanks.
고마워
진작 그래야지
-There we go.
-Now I love Vegas.
이래서 라스베이거스가 좋아
I promise you next time
I absolutely will tell you.
다음번엔 꼭 말한다고 약속할게
-"Next time"?
-So close.
다음번?
문턱까지 갔는데
There won't be a next time.
You cannot see him again.
다음번은 없어
앞으로 만나지 마
I cannot see him?
You can't tell me what to do.
만나지 마?
- 나한테 명령해도 돼?
- 어쩌나? 방금 했는데
That's funny, I think I just did.
If you act like this,
I won't be around you.
밤새 이럴 거면
우리 따로 놀자
-Fine.
-Happy anniversary!
- 그거 좋지
- 좋아, 기념일 잘 보내
얘들이 정말 왜 이럴까
무슨 큰 오해가 있나보다
Guys, please! Come on, come on.
This is obviously
a misunderstanding.
No, it is not.
- 오해는 무슨 오해
- 뭔 소리야?
Don't look at me.
I just work here.
어허, 나한테 이러지 마
난 그냥 여기 직원이야
Okay, Ross? I'm a little warm,
so I'm gonna be taking off my sweater.
저기, 로스?
나 좀 더워서
스웨터 벗을 거거든
Now, I'm just letting you know...
그니까...
사랑의 육체적 행위를
요구하는 게 절대 아냐
...this is not an invitation
to the physical act of love.
그래, 아주 신났구나
Yep, that's hilarious.
I'm sorry. I'm done. I'm done.
미안, 이제 그만 할게
모르나 본데 어젯밤 일은
너한테도 창피한 일이야
You know, last night was
embarrassing for you too.
그럴 리가 있나
No, not really. You've seen me naked
hundreds of times.
넌 나 벗은 거
수백 번도 더 봤잖아
- 공개된 알몸은 처음이지
- 알았어
But it was a first for the rest
of my building.
그건 사실이지만 난
얼굴이 좀 두꺼운 편이야
That's true. But I just don't embarrass
that easily.
- 창피하면서 뭘 그래
- 아니라니까
What? You totally get embarrassed.
No, I don't. Ross, I think I'm just
a more secure person than you are.
난 너보다 정서가
안정됐나 봐
-ls that so?
-Yeah.
- 그러십니까?
- 그럼
Hey, lady!
보쇼, 아가씨!
I don't care how much
you want it, okay?
당신이 얼마나 굶었든 간에
I am not gonna have sex
with you in the bathroom!
화장실에서 댁이랑
섹스 할 생각 없수다!
You know, in Roman times,
this was more than just a hat.
로마시대엔 이게
단순한 모자가 아니었어
-Really?
-Yeah, sure, sure.
- 진짜?
- 그렇다니까
They would scrub the floors.
이걸로 바닥을 문지르고
They'd use it to get the mud
off their shoe.
신발에 묻은 진흙을
털어 내기도 하고
Sometimes underneath
the horse would get dirty.
가끔 말 아랫도리가
지저분해지면
So they would stick it right
- 이걸 집어넣고...
- 야, 알았어
I can't believe this is how
I'm spending my anniversary.
우리 1주년이 이렇게
될 줄은 상상도 못했어
그럼 나랑 좋은 데 가자, 봐
누가 팁 100달러 주더라
I'll take you someplace nice.
A guy tipped me $100.
블랙잭 한 시간 하고
5천 달러를 땄대
He was playing blackjack
for an hour and he won $5000.
Can you believe that?
믿어지냐? 5천 달러야
If I won $5000, I'd join a gym.
나한테 5천 달러 생기면
헬스클럽에 등록해서
Build up my upper body...
갑빠 좀 조성하고
...and hit Richard from behind
with a stick.
막대기로 리처드
뒤통수를 때릴 거야
Wait! Why don't I just
do what that guy did?
잠깐, 나라고 못 하란 법 있냐?
I'll take this $100,
turn it into $5000...
이 100달러로
5천 달러를 만들고
...and I'll turn that into enough
to get my movie going!
내친 김에 제작비 마련해서
촬영 다시 시작하는 거야
Good luck.
행운을 빈다
I don't need luck.
I've thought this through.
행운이 왜 필요해?
계획이 철저한데
I see.
- 알았다
- 그럼
- 고마워요
Thanks.
정말 미치겠다
이건 최악의 밤이야
I can't believe this.
This is like the worst night ever.
그냥 너랑 챈들러 사이에
약간 문제가 생긴 거야
You had a minor setback
in your relationship.
기껏해야 챈들러잖아
Big deal.
It's only Chandler.
I am so sorry.
정말 안타까운 일이다
말도 안 돼
그런 바보 같은 일로
This is crazy.
Such a stupid argument....
리처드 다시 볼 생각도 없는데
I don't wanna see Richard.
So go fix it.
그럼 가서 화해해
챈들러는 아마
너희 방에 있을 거야
Find Chandler.
He's probably in your room.
사과하고 사랑한다고 해
Tell him sorry and you love him.
네 말이 맞다
You're right, Phoebe.
- 고마워
- 뭘
-Thank you.
-Sure.
아싸! 라스베이거스 넘버원!
Yeah! Las Vegas! Number one!
이거 잃어버린 분 없어요?
Anybody lose this?
Coming out.
Place your bet.
됐습니다, 걸어주세요
Dice her out.
주사위 나갑니다
옐로 11, 앞줄에 지급
Yellow 11. Pay the front line!
So I'm on my way back to the bathroom.
저기...
나 지금 화장실 가는 중인데
네, 알았어요
가던 길 쭉 가세요
All right, all right.
Just keep walking, all right?
로스, 너 지금...
What are you?
I am sorry, sir.
죄송해요, 선생님이
정말 맘에 드나봐요
I think he just really likes you.
저기
You know that teacher who had a baby
with her student?
제자랑 연애해서 아이 가진
여선생 얘기 알죠?
뭐야, 이게...
- 여기요
- 무슨 일이죠?
-Can I help you?
-Yes.
네, 죄송한데
바지 남는 거 있나요?
Do you have any extra pants? My friend
seems to have had a little accident.
친구가 실수를 한 것 같네요
-Can I change $100?
-Changing $100.
100달러요
100달러 교환
-Good luck, sir.
-Thanks.
- 행운을 빕니다
- 고마워요
That's right.
이겁니다
-Thirteen.
-Hit me!
한 장 더
Oh, man!
아뿔싸!
Wait!
잠깐!
챈들러, 너무 엄청난 사건이야
You are not gonna believe this!
I have found my identical hand twin.
내 일란성 손 쌍둥이를 발견했어
What?
뭐?
My identical hand twin!
일란성 손 쌍둥이
What's an identical hand twin?
- 일란성 손 쌍둥이가 뭔데?
- 말 그대로
What does it sound like?
It's a guy with my identical hands.
내 손이랑 똑같은 손을 가진 남자
It was incredible. The dealer's hands
were exactly like mine.
놀랍게도 그 딜러의 손이
내 손이랑 똑같더라고
It was like looking
at my hands in a mirror!
내 손을 거울로
보는 것 같더라니까
You sure you weren't
looking at your hands in a mirror?
확실해? 네 손을
거울로 본 게 아니고?
Don't you see what this means?
I can forget about that stupid movie.
무슨 뜻인지 모르겠어?
바보 같은 영화는 때려치울래
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
백만장자가 될 테니까
어떻게?
-How?
-I don't have it all worked out yet.
아직 구체적인 계획은 없지만
But it's gotta mean big money.
Come on, identical hands!
큰돈을 벌 수 있어
손이 똑같다니까
Again, I must go back to...
다시 이걸로 돌아가자...
어떻게?
...how?
This is Vegas, man.
People will pay to see freaky stuff!
여긴 라스베이거스야
희한한 건 장사가 돼
너 같으면 이 손을
보는 데 얼마 낼래
How much would you pay
to see this hand...
...twice?
것도 두 번씩
I can't really put a price on that.
난 도저히 값을 못 매기겠다
Are you un-supporting me again?
너 또 내 일에 딴지 거냐?
아냐, 아니지
I support you 100%.
I just didn't get it right away.
널 전적으로 지지하는데
다만 이해를 못했던 거야
Now I'm caught up.
이제 알겠네
일란성 손 쌍둥이
Identical hand twins.
It's a million-dollar idea!
- 백만 달러짜리 아이디어다
- 그렇지?
Right? I know.
Okay. All right.
그럴 줄 알았어
What's that for?
그건 뭔데?
Well, I gotta document this
before that dealer gets off his break.
그 딜러 자리 비우기 전에
기록으로 남겨둬야지
알았다
- 안녕
- 피비
I found my identical hand twin!
내 일란성 손 쌍둥이를 찾았어
Oh, you're so lucky!
너 운 억세게 좋다
근데 모니카는 어디 있어?
둘이 화해했어?
So where's Monica?
Did you guys make up?
아니
But she just came up here.
- 좀 전에 올라왔는데
- 그건 조이였어
That was Joey.
어디로 갔지? 이상하네
I wonder where she is?
It's so weird.
아마 리처드랑 놀고 있겠지
She's probably talking to Richard.
Would you stop that?
제발 그만 좀 할래?
You know what she said
after her lunch with Richard?
그날 점심 먹고 들어와서
처음 한 소리가 뭔지 알아?
She didn't feel anything for him.
She loves you.
아무 느낌도 없더래
걔는 널 사랑해
-Really?
-Yes.
- 정말?
- 그럼
She feels terrible. She really wants
to make up. You've gotta find her.
지금 걔 기분 엉망이야
화해하고 싶댔으니까
빨리 찾아봐
그래
- 알았어
- 그래야지
Good.
I should really start wearing hats.
나도 모자 좀 써봐야겠다
Welcome to Las Vegas.
라스베이거스에 잘 오셨어요
-Did you enjoy your flight?
-I did.
여행 즐거우셨어요?
그럼요, 덕분에 너무 좋았어요
Thank you very much.
It was excellent.
-I hope you had a nice flight.
-Oh, it was the best.
- 즐거운 여행 되셨길 바랍니다
- 오, 최고였어요
I think the check-in is that way.
프런트는 저쪽 같은데
안녕
애들은 날 너무 좋아해
Kids love me.
얘들아!
Hi, you guys are here!
- 피비!
- 너희들 왔구나!
What'd you do?
Did you go to a costume party?
근데 너희들
가장무도회에 갔었니?
Let me guess.
Pancho Villa.
내가 맞혀볼게
넌 판초빌라
그리고 넌... 밥 사겟
And you're Bob Saget.
Pancho Villa?
- 판초빌라?
- 그래
무슨 소리야, 내가 왜...
What are you talking about, Phoebe?
I don't
Oh, my God! You drew on me?
내 얼굴에 낙서를 해?
넌 내 바지에 물 쏟았잖아
Hey, you wet my pants!
What kind of party was this?
무슨 파티였는데 그래?
나 계속 이러고 다닌 거야?
너 이건 정말 심했어
I've been walking around like this?
You have so crossed a line.
Rach, wait.
The men's room is that way.
레이첼, 잠깐만
남자화장실은 저쪽이야
왜?
It's the third time she's won
on a machine I was playing.
내가 하던 기계인데 저 할머니
벌써 세 번째 터뜨리잖아
I bet she's one of those people.
아마 그쪽 사람일 거야
비, 비밀공작원?
Mole people?
What? No, a lurker.
- 아니, 얌체족
- 얌체족이 뭔데?
What's that?
When you're playing a machine
and it hasn't paid out...
누가 슬롯머신에서
계속 잃고 있을 때
...a lurker waits for you
to give up and then
얌체족은 그 사람이
포기하길 기다렸다가...
Kills you?
죽여버려?
아니, 살짝 끼어들어서
잭팟을 훔쳐가지
They swoop in and steal your jackpot.
-How do you know about this?
-My nana used to do it.
- 어떻게 그런 걸 다 알아?
- 우리 할머니 수법이거든
That's how she paid for my dance
Karate lessons.
그런 식으로 내 댄스...
가라데 교습비를 마련하셨지
Dance karate?
댄스 가라데?
Yes, it's a deadly...
그래... 치명적이지만
아름다운 스포츠지
...but beautiful sport.
어쩔래
안 지워져
-lt won't come off.
-What?
- 뭐?
- 안 지워진다니까
It won't come off.
Oh, my God. Rach, are you sure?
세상에, 레이첼
정말이야?
I took it off
and then I drew it back on.
아니, 지워졌는데
내가 다시 그렸다
Rach, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sure we can get it off, okay?
레이첼, 정말 미안하다
내가 책임지고 지워줄게
-Just give me your pen.
-Why? What are you gonna do?
- 펜이나 내놔
- 그건 왜, 어쩌려고?
Well, I believe I'm going
to stab you repeatedly.
너 죽을 때까지 쑤실 거다
Not here. There are cameras everywhere.
여기선 안 돼
카메라 쫙 깔렸어
야, 너희들 왔구나!
You made it!
- 조이!
- 임마, 로스!
- 반갑다
- 이 친구 누구야? 멋지다
Who's your friend?
He's hot.
Thanks, man.
고맙다
Listen, I talked to Chandler.
And I'm sorry about the movie.
챈들러한테 영화 얘기
들었는데 정말 유감이다
Don't be sorry.
그럴 거 없어
I don't need it anymore.
I found my identical hand twin.
영화 따윈 아무래도 좋아
내 손 쌍둥이를 찾았거든
Your what?
- 너의 뭐?
- 내 일란성 손 쌍둥이
My identical hand twin.
The person whose hands are like mine.
나랑 손이 똑같은 사람이야
-Were you looking for this person?
-Not even. This thing is a gold mine.
그 사람을 찾고 있었니?
그럴 리가 있나
이건 노다지야
뭐?
What?
그게 무슨 돈이 되냐?
That won't make you any money.
그래, 좋을 대로 생각해
Well, fine.
None of you will live with me
in my hand-shaped mansion.
손 모양으로 대형맨션 지어도
너흰 절대 안 받아줄 테니까
Except you.
You can live in the thumb.
피비만 빼고
넌 엄지에서 살아
All right, baby, come on!
좋았어, 가자!
그렇지! 오늘 불붙었다!
I am on fire!
See you later.
나중에 보자, 모니카
What are you doing?
챈들러, 뭐하는 거야?
What's it look like?
Going home.
- 뭐 같아? 나 집에 간다
- 왜?
Why?
챈들러
Wait. Sorry, I was just playing
for one second.
챈들러, 기다려
미안해, 잠깐 한 거야
널 찾던 중이었어
If you don't want me to see
Richard again, I won't.
그렇게 싫으면 다신 안 만날게
아무 의미도 없는 사람이야
He means nothing to me.
Oh, come on. I was there.
왜 이래, 나도 다 봤는데
I know he's the love of your life.
많이 좋아했던 거 알고 있어
Not anymore.
이젠 아냐
Really?
정말?
Really.
정말이야
All right?
괜찮지?
집 같은 건 잊어버리고
우리 1주년을 축하하자
Let's forget about going home
and celebrate our anniversary.
Okay, this is empty.
비었네?
I wanted to make a dramatic scene,
but I hate packing.
극적인 장면을 연출하고는
싶었지만 짐 싸는 건 싫어
Where's the other guy?
- 다른 사람은 어디 있죠?
- 다른 사람이라뇨?
Which guy?
훤칠하고 검은 머리에
손이 나랑 똑같이 생겼어요
Tall, dark hair, hand looks
exactly like this?
I don't know about the hands,
but he went to the restroom.
손은 잘 모르지만 방금 여기
있던 사람은 화장실에 갔어요
How you doing?
안녕하쇼?
-Very busy.
-Right. Okay.
- 아주 바쁘네요
- 네, 알았어요
Yes, hello. I have a question.
네, 수고하십니다
문의할 게 좀 있어서요
I used your pen to draw
on my friend's face.
제가 귀사의 펜으로
친구 얼굴에 낙서를 했거든요
A beard and a mustache.
턱수염이랑 콧수염
Thank you.
감사합니다
No, she didn't think so.
아뇨, 본인은 그렇게
생각하지 않아요
I know. It's like
Anyway....
그럼요, 꼭...
어쨌거나
Makeup didn't cover it, we've tried
everything and nothing's worked.
메이크업으로도 안 가려지고
도무지 지울 방법이 없네요
What do we do?
어떻게 해야 되죠?
네
그래요
알겠습니다
Thank you.
네, 감사합니다
Yeah, it's not coming off.
그거 안 지워진대
What? What else did he say?
뭐? 그 말밖에 안 해?
뭐라고 했냐면
나더러 재미있는 사람이래
He said he thought I was funny.
Okay, look.
Let's just go downstairs...
그래, 어디 보자...
아래층에 내려가서 신나게
놀다보면 다 잊어먹을 거야
...we'll have some fun
and you will forget all about it.
안 돼, 이런 꼴을 하고
밖에 나갈 순 없어
There's no way I am leaving
looking like this!
Come on, Rach. It's not that bad.
왜 이래, 그렇게 심하진 않아
Ross, I am a human doodle!
난 인간 낙서판이야!
Just because some idiot drew on your
face doesn't mean you can't have fun.
어떤 바보가 얼굴에 낙서
좀 했다고 풀죽으면 쓰나
게다가, 이거 봐
Besides, no one will
even look at you.
아무도 널 쳐다보진 않아
여긴 라스베이거스라고
This is Vegas. Hello?
There are tons of other freaks here.
너 말고도 구경거리 엄청 많아
구경거리 엄청 많아
'너 말고도'는 취소
There are tons of freaks here.
No other. No.
Come on. No one will notice. I swear.
아무도 모를 거야
내가 약속할게
가자
그래, 더러는 쳐다보고
손가락질도 하네
There was some staring and pointing.
나 술 한잔할래
I need a drink.
어? 그거 손댔다간
큰 덤터기 쓰는데
They really overcharge you
for that stuff.
하긴 무슨 상관이야?
다 내가 낼 건데
But who cares,
because it's all on me.
That is one big drink.
한잔치고는 굉장히 많다
Macadamia nut?
마카다미아 땅콩?
Wow! That's some pricey nut.
와우! 욜라 비싼 땅콩이네
Really like those macadamia nuts?
마카다미아 땅콩
진짜 좋아하는구나
Nope.
아니
Get out of here, you lurker!
저리 가, 얌체족
Go on, get!
먹고 떨어져라
- 안녕, 피비
- 잘됐구나
You made up.
I couldn't be mad at him
for too long.
네가 져줘야지 어떡하겠어
She couldn't live
without the "Chand love."
챈들러표 사랑 없인
못사는 여자니까
그래, 방 잡아라
Get a room.
-We have one.
-Use it.
- 벌써 잡았어
- 알아, 그 방 쓰라고
안녕, 챈들러
안녕, 모니카
Bye, Chandler. Bye, Mon.
손님 중에 피비라는 분은
구내전화를 받아주세요
Phoebe, Phoebe. Please pick up
a house phone.
챈들러와 모니카의 전화입니다
You have a call from Chandler and Mon.
Hello, Chandler and Mon.
Hello?
챈들러랑 모니카니?
여보세요
이 치사한 얌체족아!
You dirty lurker!
I'm sorry, you are the same old lady, right?
Yeah. Dirty lurker!
죄송해요
아까 그 할머니 맞죠?
치사한 얌체족!
그렇지
That's right.
Take good care of those babies.
맞아요, 그렇게
소중히 다뤄야죠
Excuse me?
네?
It's me. Joey.
- 나예요, 조이
- 절 아세요?
Do I know you?
Joey?
조이...
아, 네...
그 손 아저씨군요
Yeah, the hand guy.
그래서 이 쌍둥이 손으로
뭘 하는 게 좋겠어요?
So, what are we gonna do
about this hand twin thing?
Nothing.
할 게 없는데?
Look, you and I have been given a gift.
이봐요, 당신이랑 난
선물을 받은 거예요
받았으면 활용을 해야죠
예를 들어 손 모델
We have to do something with it.
Like hand modeling. Or magic.
마술이라든지
And you know NASA's
gonna want to talk to us.
NASA에서 섭외가
들어올지 알아요?
I have to get back to work.
그만 가볼게요
우리들만의 쇼도 가능해요
We can have our own show.
We can clap our hands together.
People will love it!
우리가 박수를 치면
다들 좋아할 거예요
And I wrote a song for us.
주제가도 만들었어요
This hand is your hand
이 손은 너의 손
This hand is my hand
이 손은 나의 손
Oh, wait, that's your hand
아차, 그건 너의 손
No, wait, it's my hand
아차차, 그건 나의 손
좋잖아요
됐어요
-That's okay.
-But you haven't even heard the chorus!
코러스도 있어요
Oh, my God.
맙소사
I look like my great-aunt Muriel.
꼭 뮤리엘 대고모님 같네
All right, you know what?
이렇게 하자
We don't have to go downstairs.
우리가 내려갈 필요 없어
We can bring Vegas up to us.
라스베이거스를
이리 대령시키지 뭐
All right, come on.
자, 시작할게
블랙잭이야
We'll play some blackjack.
Here we go.
돌린다
-Thirteen.
-Hit me.
- 13
- 하나 더
Twenty-three.
우... 23이네
Which is what we play to
at this casino!
이 카지노의 규칙에 따라...
You win 10 dollars!
10달러 따셨습니다
-I bet 20.
-Right.
- 20달러 걸었어
- 그렇군요
A new pair of shoes
for the Chan-Chan man!
'챈챈맨'의 꼬까신발을 위해
- 좋았어!
- 그렇지!
I've never seen a roll like this!
이런 대박은 평생 처음이야
That's right, baby!
누가 아니래, 내 새끼!
What do I want now?
자, 이제 뭘로 할까
알았어
어... 8?
Eight?
어... 6?
-Six.
-Pick a number! That is your only job.
숫자만 찍어
다른 건 안 시켜
-Eight.
-Thank you.
- 8로 가자
- 고마워
If you get this,
we buy everybody a steak dinner.
이번에도 걸리면 모두에게
스테이크 하나씩 돌린다
Eight it is.
8입니다
- 잘했어!
- 그렇지! 좋았어!
We're not buying steak dinners, are we?
스테이크 진짜로
사는 건 아니겠지?
-No.
-Okay, good.
- 당연하지
- 좋아
-What do I want now?
-Try a hard eight.
그래, 이번엔?
- 하드 8로 해봐
- 뭐?
-What?
-Two fours.
- 4 두 개
- 알았어
Eight!
8입니다
Don't you let her go.
You're a lucky guy.
그 여자 놓치지 말게
운 좋은 친구 같으니
감사합니다
주정뱅이 도박꾼 아저씨
Thank you, Mr. Drunken Gambler.
You get this and we get
the biggest suite in the place.
좋아, 이번에 성공하면
여기서 제일 큰
특실을 얻는 거야
어허, 왜들 이러실까
We get the biggest suite in the place.
'우리만' 특실에 들어가요
The biggest suite in the place!
좋아, 제일 큰 특실 나가신다
Come on!
아싸! 사랑해, 우리가
대체 왜 싸운 거지?
I love you!
I can't remember why we fought.
Because I had lunch with Rich
내가 리처드랑 점심...
Me neither!
나도 몰라!
-What now?
-Another hard eight.
- 좋아, 이제 뭘 할까?
- 또 하드 8
Hard eight?
Let's call it easy eight!
하드 8? 쉬운 8이겠지
I'll tell you what.
You roll another hard eight...
좋아, 이렇게 하자
또 하드 8이 나오면...
...and we get married here tonight.
우리 오늘밤 여기서 결혼하자
굴려라, 굴려라, 굴려라
Shut up!
시끄러워요!
It just got interesting!
재미는 이제부터예요!
What did you say?
방금 뭐라고 했지?
You roll another hard eight,
we get married tonight.
하드 8을 또 성공시키면
오늘밤 여기서 결혼한다고
You serious?
진심이야?
Yes. I love you.
그래, 난 널 사랑해
I've never loved anybody
as much as I love you.
어느 누구보다 널 사랑해
I've never loved anybody
as much as I love you.
나도 이런 사랑은 처음이야
So if an eight comes up,
we take it as a sign and we do it.
좋아, 만일 8이 나오면
신의 계시로 알고 결혼하자
What do you say?
어때?
- 좋아
- 그래
하드 8
무효
That's a four.
좋아, 하나는 4
다른 하나는 어디 있죠?
-And where's the other one?
-Under the table.
테이블 밑으로 들어갔는데
Nobody move!
You look that way, I look this way.
다들 꼼짝 말아요!
- 넌 저쪽, 난 이쪽
- 알았어
Here it is, here it is.
여기 있다
That could be 4 or 5.
4도 되고 5도 되는데
It's your call.
네가 선택해
It's a four.
이건 4야
I think so too.
나도 그렇게 생각해
Oh, well, lost again.
이런, 또 망했네
That's it. You and me. Outside!
잡았다, 같이 좀 나갑시다!
I wouldn't want you to lose a chunk
of that pretty blond hair!
그 예쁜 금발 한 움큼
뽑히는 건 보기 싫은데
Be cool.
잠깐 대기
Okay, your lurking days are over.
이제 얌체족 생활도
끝난 줄 알아요
What?
뭐?
이제부터 매번 내가
선수를 칠 테니까
Everyone you lurk,
I'll lurk first.
You move on,
I'll be one step ahead of you...
언제나 아줌마보다 한발 앞서
손을 쓸 거니까 두고보라구요
...every single time.
And then I'll be on your ass
every hour of every day...
매일 매순간 아줌마
꽁무니를 쫓아다닐 거야
...till Monday...
월요일까지만
...because that's when I go home.
왜냐면 내가 그때 집에 가니까
When do you leave?
아줌마는 언제 가죠?
Also Monday.
나도 월요일이야
몇 시죠? 시간 맞으면
택시나 합승하게
What time? Maybe we can share a cab.
Hit me.
하나 더
We need more cards.
카드가 부족해
Yeah. And we also need more drinks.
Hold on a second.
술도 좀 부족한데
잠깐만 기다려
어럽쇼? 됐다
Hello, Vegas?
여보셔, 라스베이거스, 네
We would like more alcohol.
여기 알코올이 더 필요한데
안주로 맥주도 좀 갖다 주시고
You know what else?
We would like some more beers.
여보세요?
번호도 안 누르고 뭐하니
Oh, I forgot to dial.
That must be our alcohol and beers.
우리 알코올이랑 맥주 왔다
내가 사랑하는 조이다!
It's Joey! I love Joey!
나도 조이 사랑하지
조이는 오리랑 산대
Oh, I love Joey!
Joey lives with a duck.
- 안녕
- 이리 온
그건 그렇고 나 좀 도와주라
Look, I need some help, okay?
Someone has to convince
my hand twin to cooperate.
누가 손 쌍둥이 설득해서
나랑 동업 좀 하게 해줘
I'll do it. Whatever you need me to do,
I'm your man.
내가 하지 뭐
뭐든 말만 하라고
우린 친구 아니냐
Are you okay?
너 괜찮냐?
Yeah. Fine. Thanks.
그래, 괜찮아
고맙다
Hey, Rach?
헤이, 레이첼
How you doing?
안녕하쇼?
I'm doing good, baby.
How you doing?
난 안녕한데
자긴 안녕하셔?
야, 쟤 술 그만 먹여
Don't let her drink anymore.
Here's that macadamia nut.
여기 마카다미아 땅콩이오
No, something else.
얼라려? 아닌데?
So, what do you wanna do now?
그럼 이제 뭘 한다?
여기서 나가고 싶다
I wanna get out of the room.
난 말이야...
I really miss downstairs.
아래층이 왜 이리 그립냐?
Okay, you know what? There is only
one way I am leaving this hotel room.
좋아, 내가 이 호텔방에서
빠져나가는 방법은 딱 하나야
Well, hello!
- 반갑습니다
- 라스베이거스에 잘 오셨어요
I'm Ross.
전 로스예요
-Good luck to you.
-Sir, you've got a little something....
- 많이 따세요
- 아저씨 요기 뭐 묻었네
Hello.
별고 없으시지요?
안녕하세요
문안드리옵니다
안 돼!
I won!
터졌다!
I won! I finally won!
드디어 내가 터뜨렸어!
- 내 거야, 누구 동전인데
- 이거 갖고 사라져요, 아줌씨
I won! That was my quarter!
Take a hike, toots.
Excuse me, sir.
나 좀 보슈
This lady played my quarter.
This is my money.
이 여자가 내 동전을 썼다우
이건 내 돈이라니까
Is that true, miss?
사실입니까, 아가씨?
Sells drugs to kids.
- 애들한테 마약 판대요
- 네?
She sells drugs to kids.
애들한테 마약 파는 여자예요
It was my quarter.
- 내 동전이었다니까
- 저 분 동전이었나요?
Was it her quarter?
How about we talk
about this over dinner?
저녁이나 하면서 얘기할까요?
-Okay, lady, you're out of here.
-No, you can't arrest me!
좋습니다, 나가주시죠
안 돼요! 잡아가지 마세요!
난 그 지옥에 못 돌아가욧!
I won't go back to that hellhole!
I'm just taking you outside.
밖으로 나가자는 겁니다
네, 알았어요
I need something old, something new,
something borrowed and something blue.
결혼하려면 오래된 것, 새것,
빌린 것, 파란 것이 꼭 있어야 돼
좋아, 알았어
이거다, 파란 것
그리고 새것
Here's something blue and new.
You are so efficient.
I love you.
똑똑하긴, 사랑해
-Let's go.
-No, wait!
- 가자
- 아니, 잠깐!
We need something old.
오래된 게 없잖아
좋아, 12살 때부터 지갑에
넣고 다니던 콘돔이 있는데
I have a condom in my wallet
that I've had since I was twelve.
That'll work.
그것도 돼
I don't think so.
난 영 아닌데
좋아, 그럼 이제 빌린 것
Now something borrowed.
Here, just take this.
그냥 이걸 갖고 가자
That's stealing.
이건 도둑질이야
We'll bring it back.
Put it under your dress.
다시 돌려줄 거야
빨랑 옷 속에 넣어
Okay. One thing at a time.
좋아, 차근차근 하자고
-Are you gonna play?
-No, I don't really have any money.
- 게임 하실 건가요?
- 아뇨, 난 돈이 없어요
Not yet, anyway.
아직은 없다는 뜻이죠
Can't sit here if you don't play.
그럼 비켜주십시오
안녕하세요
레지나 팔랑지라고 해요
My name is Regina Falangie.
I'm a businesswoman
in town on business.
시내에서 비즈니스를 하는
비즈니스우먼이죠
Would you like to see my card?
명함 한 장 드릴까요?
이런, 다이어리를 어쨌더라?
B 회의실에 두고 왔나봐요
What did I do with my Filofax?
I must've left it
in Conference Room B.
-Fourteen.
-Hit me.
- 14입니다
- 하나 더
Oh, my God.
어머나!
May I just say that you two gentlemen
have the exact same hands?
두 분의 손이 너무나 똑같다는
말씀을 드려도 될는지요
구별이 안 되네요
They're identical.
비즈니스업계에서는
이런 걸 본 적이 없어요
I've never seen that
in the business world.
Stop it.
그만하시죠
팔랑지 양?
Miss Falangie, may I ask you a question
as an impartial person at this table?
이 테이블의 제3자 입장에서
한 가지 대답해주시겠어요?
Please stop it.
제발 그만!
Wouldn't you pay good money
to see identical hands...
이 쌍둥이 손이 공연물
형식으로 공개된다면
...showcased in some type
of an entertainment venue?
돈을 지불할 용의가
있으신가요?
If you leave now, I will chop off
my hand and give it to you!
당장 여기서 떠나준다면
내 손을 잘라서 드리리다
Didn't I just throw you out?
방금 쫓겨난 분 아닌가요?
No, you threw out Phoebe.
아뇨, 쫓겨난 건 피비죠
난 레지나 팔랑지예요, 팔랑지!
I'm Regina Falangie. Falangie.
Come on, lady.
갑시다, 아가씨
Please take him too.
제발 이 친구도 데려가 줘
Me? Oh, come on, man.
나요?
- 왜 이래요...
- 자, 나갑시다
Come on, buddy.
너무하는 거 아니에요?
Don't let him do this. Come on!
우린 손 쌍둥이라니깐
I'm your hand twin!
Hello. One marriage, please.
결혼식 하나 부탁해요
We want to get married.
네, 우리 결혼할 거예요
There's a service in progress.
Have a seat.
지금 식이 진행 중이니
앉아서 기다리시죠
All right.
그러죠 뭐
What are you doing?
그게 뭔데?
The "Wedding March."
Does that freak you out?
웨딩마치야
왜, 긴장돼?
No, it's the graduation song.
아니, 그건 졸업축가잖아
좋았어, 올 것이 왔군
This is it.
We're gonna get married.
우리 결혼한다
You sure you wanna do this?
정말 후회 안 할 거야?
Hello, Mrs. Ross!
안녕하세요, 로스 부인
Well, hello, Mr. Rachel!
안녕하세요, 레이첼 씨
Wait. Okay.
잠깐, 됐다